<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<update>
  <dev>Hootan Parsa</dev>
  <site>http://forum.xda-developers.com/showthread.php?t=1523691</site>
  <code>201501051</code>
  <name>MiXplorer v5.0.23 (201501051)</name>
  <link>http://forum.xda-developers.com/attachment.php?attachmentid=3098813</link>
  <log>
    Notice: Version 4.x plugins are not compatible anymore!
    - Auto-update removed. So please follow MiXplorer@twitter.com to get update notification.
    
    v5.0.23-201501051:
    - Fixed wrong offset in system files modified time.
    - Fixed wrong modified time in categories in latest builds.
    - Added Split action bar option in settings page.
    - Fixed status bar overlapping issue after changing Language or Skin.
    - Changed to display drawer over action bar and related buttons moved into drawer.
    - Changed title to "File Manager" in launcher.
    - Fixed UI glitch on selecting an items.
    
    v5.0.22-201501034:
    - Added an option to settings to show the folder path in the main bar.
    - Fixed some little bugs.

    v5.0.21-201501014
    - Fixed loading new saved skins.
    - Fixed Go-to problem in Text editor for huge text files.
    - Fixed hidden Python syntax highlighting.
    - Fixed Opening drawer while holding items to transfer between folders.
    - Fixed bug in extracting splitted zip files.
    - Fixed Transparent theme problems while starting app. (not sure, waiting for feedback ....)
    - Changed a sensitive code related to transferring Encrypted files between Networks/Clouds/Local.

    v5.0.21-201501012
    - Fixed loading skins.
    - Fixed system files modified time.
    
    v5.0.21: 
    - Optimized UI and some icons quality.
    
    v5.0.20: 
    - Changed Package name to "com.android.mixplorer".
    - Added MP3 Tag Editor.
    - Moved History inside left drawer.
    - Fixed to keep urls arrangement in History list.
    - Added Skin customization.
    - Added dual panel in landscape mode.
    - Improved to encrypt password and tokens secret in database.
    - Fixed to not create zip64 for small zip file.
    - Added Next/Previous buttons in the Properties dialog when you choose multiple files.
    - Fixed and Optimized streaming feature.
    - Made a new powerful Text Editor.
    - Improved SFTP client.
    - Optimized UI.
    - Fixed writing restriction in Kitkat.
    - Fixed share from Clouds.
    - Removed auto-update, please follow MiXplorer@twitter.com to get update notification.
    - Removed Kill the app option, you can long-press Back button.
    - And fixed other thousands bugs, I guess!
  </log>
  <donate>w.parsa@gmail.com</donate>
  <auto>true</auto>
</update>
