<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<update>
  <dev>Hootan Parsa</dev>
  <site>http://forum.xda-developers.com/showthread.php?t=1523691</site>
  <code>201501051</code>
  <name>MiXplorer v5.1.0-B201502021</name>
  <link>http://forum.xda-developers.com/attachment.php?attachmentid=3145312</link>
  <log>
    Notice: Version 4.x plugins are not compatible anymore!
    - Auto-update removed. So please follow MiXplorer@twitter.com to get update notification.
    
    v5.1.0-201502021:
    - Added Filter mode option to the main menu.
    - Fixed mp3 tag editor issue on saving.
    - Fixed Backup apk files in User and System app categories.
    - Moved overflow button to Action bar when it's in bottom mode.
    - Added option to disable swiping to right in first and to left in last tab.
    - Added Tab bar and related menu options moved to it.
    - Added some new options in tab menu.
    - Improved to select an installed language addon after we perform a clean install of app.
    - Added Share option to main menu of Text Editor.
    - Fixed to encode uris for sending files.
    - Improved to let you attach multiple files (Press Check button in top-left in action mode) when using app as a file picker. (If it's supported by the related app)
    - Improved to select one of color schemes after you import a skin package and to update UI automatically.
    - Fixed hiding soft keys in some of devices with old Android versions.
    - Added an option to change Text Editor font, in Custom Skin settings.
    - Fixed updating Media-store and Removed related option from settings.
    - Improved to find last visible item after refreshing the list.
    - Added auto thumb creator for custom skins.
    - Added Toggle View Mode in Text editor.
    - Improved to update lists automatically after changing or adding files in other apps.
    - Fixed extracting thumbnails from mp3 files. (It still has problem with some of files!)
    - Added Batch delete option for local directories.
    - Added "Select all" option to the main menu.
    - Added a separated option for customized skins in the settings page.
    - Fixed adding files, folders into a zip file.
    - Fixed WebDav bug related to providers which doesn't return creationdate property of the file.
    - Added clickable link on View mode of Text Editor.
    - Added "Clipboard" to Share options dialog.
    - Added some new options in Rename dialog.
    - Added more info about apk package in Open With... dialog, even for packages with newer sdk levels.
    - Fixed downloading some of files from Google Drive.
    - Fixed wrong syntax colors while scrolling in Text editor.
    - Added Image metadata.
    - Fixed a bug on changing and saving a text file for multiple times.
    - Added creating empty pdf, odt, docx, ods, xlsx and pptx files.
    - Added an option to hide folder icon preview in Detailed List view mode.
    - Fixed executing shell in text editor.
    - Added auto-detect encoding for Text editor.
    - Removed Baidu cloud.
    - And lots of bug fixes and tiny changes.
  </log>
  <donate>w.parsa@gmail.com</donate>
  <auto>true</auto>
</update>
